Elizabeth P. Richardson Papers, 1865-1998
Mortimer Rare Book Room, William Allan Neilson Library, Smith College
- Series IV. Subject Files, 1865-1997
  - Strachey, Marjorie. The Counterfeits. London: Longmans, Green and Co. 1927, 275 pages. photocopy. (Box 41, Folder 164)
  - Woolf, Virginia. "Julia Margaret Cameron" Victorian Pictures of Famous Men and Fair Women. Read by Elizabeth Power Richardson.
    See: Box 38, folder 147
  - Woolf, Virginia. Kew Gardens and woodcuts from Monday or Tuesday, 28 pages. photocopy. (Box 41, Folder 165)
  - Woolf, Virginia. Mrs. Dalloway and To the Lighthouse selections read by Celia Johnson. Record. New York: Caedmon Publishers 1959
  - Woolf, Virginia. A Room of One's Own. Film performed by Eileen Atkins. videocassette. (Box 41, Folder 166)
- Series V. A Bloomsbury Iconography, [1979]-[1991]
  - Early Draft, typescript, corrected 1979 Aug 4, 5 pages. (Box 42, Folder 167)
  - Draft A in 6 notebooks, typescript, corrected undated (Box 42-3, Folder 168-73)
  - Draft fragments, typescript, corrected undated (Box 43, Folder 174)
  - Draft B, typescript, corrected undated (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - Galley proofs, corrected 1988 Oct. (Box 44, Folder 176-79)
  - Galley proofs, corrected, with printer's annotations. Stamped "Jan 23 1989."
  - Original sketches by Sarah Black for "Appendix A: The Cameron Photographs of Julia Stephen" in A Bloomsbury Iconography. (Box 45, Folder 180)
  - Illustrative material (Box 45, Folder 181)
  - Permission letters.
    See: Box 4, Folder 128
  - Advertisements and Reviews 1989 May-1990 May (Box 45, Folder 182)
  - Notes on Paper Darts: The Illustrated Letters edited by Frances Spalding, typescript 1991, 2 pages. (Box 45, Folder 183)
  - (scrapbook 12A and 12S) (Box 46-47)
    A Bloomsbury Iconography. Updated by the author after publication, typescript, [1991]
- Series VI. Artwork, 1923-1996
  - Black, Sarah. Original sketches for "Appendix A: The Cameron Photographs of Julia Stephen" in A Bloomsbury Iconography.
    See: Box 45, Folder 180
  - Fry, Roger.
  - Grant, Duncan. Duncan Grant at Charleston, 19 photographic slides. (Box 48, Folder 184)
  - Kennedy, Richard.
  - Starr, Martha H. and Elizabeth W. Hill. Virginia Woolf Calendar Diary 1982. New York and London: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc. 1981 (Box 48, Folder 185)
  - Starr, Martha H. and Elizabeth W. Hill. Virginia Woolf Calendar Diary 1983. New York and London: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc. 1982, 2 copies. (Box 48, Folder 186)
- Series VII. Oversize
  - PERSONAL PAPERS
    - Pattle family trees 1985 (Box 49, Folder 187)
    - Map of Sussex, England. (Box 49, Folder 188)
  - SUBJECT FILES
    - Architectural Review, May 1930, pages 287-300. photocopy. (Box 49, Folder 189)
    - Woolf, Virginia. Mrs. Dalloway and To the Lighthouse selections read by Celia Johnson. Record. New York: Caedmon Publishers 1959 (Box 49, Folder 190)
  - A BLOOMSBURY ICONOGRAPHY
    - Galley proofs, corrected, with printer's annotations. Stamped "Jan 23 1989." (Box 49, Folder 200)
  - ARTWORK
    - The Charleston Calendar 1990 Bloomsbury Portraits by Lettice Ramsey., 2 copies. (Box 49, Folder 201)
    - The Charleston Calendar 1991 Virginia Woolf. (Box 49, Folder 202)
    - The Charleston Calendar 1992 A Bloomsbury Garden (Box 49, Folder 203)
    - The Charleston Calendar 1996 Duncan Grant and Vanessa Bell: Book Jackets., 3 copies (Box 49, Folder 204)
    - Charleston Revisited: A new view of Bloomsbury in the country. Poster for an exhibition at the Francis Kyle Gallery 1993, framed (Box 49, Folder 205)
    - Fry, Roger. Outside Avila: lithograph 1923, framed (Box 50, Folder 206)
    - Fry, Roger. Still Life 1918, Reproduction on linen, framed. Linen Union. (Box 50, Folder 207)
    - Kennedy, Richard. Virginia Woolf: lithograph undated, framed. Signed. (Box 50, Folder 208)
    - Kennedy, Richard. Virginia Woolf Setting Type: ink and graphite drawing undated, Framed. (Box 50, Folder 209)
      Illustration for Kennedy's A Boy at the Hogarth Press (London 1972).